Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 33, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: The Issue of the Shorter Workweek, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: February 1961
  - Item 15: Proceedings of Conference of Paper Box-Board Manufacturers, 1924; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 2, 1924
  - Item 16: The Six-Hour Day Proposed for Railroads, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Hours of Work and Full Production, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: L.B. Wheildon
    Notes: March 5, 1948
  - Item 18: The Medical Aspect of a Five-Day Labor Week, 1931; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Henry Keller
    Notes: April 1931
  - Item 19: The Twelve Hour Day in the Steel Industry, 1923; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America
    Notes: June 1923
  - Item 20: The Need for Research During Industrial Depression, 1931; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Social Science Research Council
  - Item 21: Short Hours Pay, 1937; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: August 1937
  - Item 22: Fact File on the Shorter Work Week, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: What is at Stake in a Shorter Work Week?, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Wage Earners View the Shorter Work Week and Other Labor Matters, 1962; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Macfadden Publications, Inc.
  - Item 25: Benjamin Graham on the Flexible Work-Year: An Answer to Unemployment, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
  - Item 26: Flextime, 1974; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 15, 1974
  - Item 27: Legal Limitations on Flexible and Compressed Work Schedules for Federal Employees, 1974; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: October 21, 1974
  - Item 28: The Shorter Work Week, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: George G. Hagedorn
    Notes: November 21, 1963
  - Item 29: Hours of Work, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Ewan Clague
    Notes: June 11, 1963
  - Item 30: What is at Stake in a Shorter Work Week?, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 31: A Quick Look at Hours Worked Under the Fair Labor Standards Act as Amended in 1966, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Box: 33, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 40 Hour Week, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Author: Institute of Public Affairs
- Box: 33, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Shorter Workweek, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Hours of Work, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Box: 33, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Earnings of Hospital Employees in New York State, 1969; Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Box: 33, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Living Conditions for Small-Wage Earners in Chicago, 1925; Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Author: Elizabeth A. Hughes
- Box: 33, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Housing in Europe, 1950; Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 10, 1950
- Box: 33, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Housing Market Analysis in Latin America, 1965; Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Box: 33, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Housing Amendment to the State Constitution, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Author: New York Division of Housing
  - Item 2: New York State Builds Homes and Helps Others to Build, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Author: Publishers Printing Company
  - Item 3: Housing Policy in the Expanding Region, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Author: The Regional Plan Association
    Notes: November 16, 1948
- Box: 33, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: One Million People in Small Houses, 1913; Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Author: Helen L. Parrish
    Notes: February 1913
- Box: 33, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Housing Policy, 1945; Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Box: 33, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report of the Latin American Seminar on Housing Statistics and Programmes, 1962; Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Notes: September 2-25, 1962
- Box: 33, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Housing After World War I, 1945; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: National Housing Agency
    Notes: December 1945
  - Item 2: Housing: Puny Giant, 1947; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Wall Street Journal
  - Item 3: The Role of the Housebuilding Industry, 1942; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Natural Resources Planning Board
    Notes: July 1942
  - Item 4: Housing America, 1940; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: National Council for the Social Studies
  - Item 5: General Housing Bill, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Citizens National Committee
  - Item 6: Reference and Source Material on Housing and Housing Needs, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. National Housing Agency
    Notes: March 1946
  - Item 7: Veterans Emergency Housing Program, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Veterans Emergency Housing Program, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Notes: November 7, 1946
  - Item 9: National Housing Act as Amended, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. Federal Housing Administration
    Notes: August 1, 1946
  - Item 10: The Lanham Act, as Amended, 1943; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Notes: September 15, 1943
- Box: 33, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Reading List on Housing, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Housing and Home Finance Agency
    Notes: May 21, 1948
  - Item 2: Bibliography on Public Housing and Related Subjects, 1945; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Reading List on Housing in the United States, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Housing Management for Government-Assisted Housing: A Selected Bibliography, 1974; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: Harriet L. Budke
    Notes: May 1974
- Box: 33, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the Housing and Urban Development Act of 1965, Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Banking and Currency
    Notes: August 11, 1965
- Box: 33, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Migrant Farmworker Housing in Oregon, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Home Building for Wage Earners, Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Author: Fred T. Ley & Co.
  - Item 3: The Kohlers of Kohler: Acculturation in a Company Town, 1971; Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Author: William R. Johnson
- Box: 33, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: How to Get Other Reports, Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Man on the Assembly Line, Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Author: Charles R. Walker & Robert H. Guest
  - Item 3: Royal Naval Personnel Research Committee Habitability Sub-Committee, 1947; Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Author: N.H. Mackworth
    Notes: August 21, 1947
  - Item 4: Fitting the Job to the Worker, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development
- Box: 33, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Bibliography of Human Engineering Reports, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Author: U.S. Naval Training Device Center
    Notes: July 15, 1961
- Box: 33, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The New Year's Eve Incident; Huntington, WV, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Author: West Virginia Human Rights Commission
    Notes: January 14, 1966
- Box: 33, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Problems of Health Conservation, 1934; Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
    Author: Milbank Memorial Fund
    Notes: March 14-15, 1934
- Box: 33, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Health Programs and Economic Development, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Author: Rashi Fein
  - Item 2: Toward Better National Health, 1938; Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Author: Interdepartmental Committee to Coordinate Health and Welfare Activities
    Notes: July 18-20, 1938
  - Item 3: Health for Millions, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Author: Cooperative Health Federation of America
    Notes: August 1946
- Box: 33, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Health in Our Time, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
    Author: F.R. Luke
  - Item 2: The Health of the Nation, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Box: 33, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Planning, Organization and Administration of National Rehabilitation Programmes for the Disabled in Developing Countries, 1971; Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
    Notes: September 27 - October 6, 1971
- Box: 33, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Health Resorts for the Working People, 1954; Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
    Author: A. Tretyakov
- Box: 33, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Nation's Health, 1939; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Interdepartmental Committee to Coordinate Health and Welfare Activities
  - Item 2: Planning for Health Services, Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Addenda to a Report for the Technical Committee on Medical Care, 1938; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Notes: July 20, 1938
  - Item 4: The Next Steps in Public Health, 1936; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Good Health is Good Business, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Notes: February 1948
  - Item 6: Evaluation Schedule of the American Public Health Association, Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Author: American Public Health Association
  - Item 7: Our National Health Problem, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Roads to Better Health, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Box: 33, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Foundation for All Our Aspirations, Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Box: 33, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Prolonged Non-Occupational Illness, 1952; Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Prolonged Non-Occupational Illness, 1952; Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Box: 33, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Plan, Operation, and Response Results of a Program of Children's Examinations, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Box: 33, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: State Institutional Employee Maintenance, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 33)
    Author: The Council of State Governments
- Box: 33, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Rules Governing Practice Before Industrial Commission, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 34)
    Author: Illinois Industrial Commission
    Notes: October 1, 1949
- Box: 33, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Incentive Practices as Viewed by Scientists and Managers of Pharmaceutical Laboratories, Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: Albert B. Chalupsky
  - Item 2: Preliminary Presentation of Data Gathered on a Survey of Office Incentives in the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: J.J. Jehring
  - Item 3: Sochetanie Material'nyk I Moral'nykh Stimulov V Razvitii Proizvodstva, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: M.P. Sakov
  - Item 4: Guidelines for the Design of New Careers, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: El Problema de los Incentivos en Cuba, Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: Carmelo Mesa-Lago
  - Item 6: Stimulating the Will to Learn; Employee Training Incentives, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: Homer T. Rosenberger
  - Item 7: Trud, Poisk, Initsialiva, 1965; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: S.I. Chibisou
  - Item 8: Wynagradzanie Wynalazcow I Racjonalizatorow, 1965; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: Andrzej Lopalewski
    Language: Polish.
  - Item 9: Incentives in the Paint and Varnish Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: Free Men for Better Job Performance, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: C.L. Dickinson
  - Item 11: Free Men for Better Job Performance, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: Financial Incentives in the Smaller Business, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: D.C. Corner
  - Item 13: Teamwork Incentives, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Author: William J. Howell
- Box: 33, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Notes and Problems in National Income Analysis, 1972; Publication (Box 33, Folder 36)
    Author: Philip H. Siegel
  - Item 2: Structural Aspects of Stability in Aggregative Income Distribution, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 36)
    Author: W. Baldamus
    Notes: March 1961
- Box: 33, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Pattern of Income, Expenditure and Consumption of African Middle Income Workers in Nairobi, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 37)
    Author: Government of Kenya
  - Item 2: Urban Consumer Surveys in Nigeria, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 37)
    Author: Federation of Nigeria
- Box: 33, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Wages - Fog or Facts?, 1965; Publication (Box 33, Folder 38)
    Author: David Layton
- Box: 33, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Louisiana Income and Employment, 1971; Publication (Box 33, Folder 39)
    Author: Louisiana Department of Employment Security
    Notes: May 1971
- Box: 33, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Personal Income in Nebraska and Nebraska Countries, 1965; Publication (Box 33, Folder 40)
    Author: Wallace C. Peterson
- Box: 33, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Income and Employment in New Mexico, 1965-1966, 1968; Publication (Box 33, Folder 41)
    Author: Linda L. DeBerry & Ralph L. Edgel
- Box: 33, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Industrialization and the Distribution of Wealth in Peru, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 42)
    Author: David Chaplin
- Box: 33, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Gross Product of Puerto Rico, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 43)
    Author: Daniel Creamer & Henrietta L. Creamer
- Box: 34, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personal Income in 1965 of Male War Veterans, Post-Korean Conflict Veterans, and Nonveterans, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: U.S. Veterans Administration
    Notes: October 20, 1967
  - Item 2: An Income-Net Worth Approach to Measuring Economic Welfare, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Burton A. Weisbrod & W. Lee Hansen
  - Item 3: Personal Income in 1966 of Male War Veterans, Post-Korean Conflict Veterans, and Nonveterans Related to Work Experience, 1969; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 18, 1969
  - Item 4: Family Income in Relation to Selected Health Characteristics, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Low-Income Families and Economic Stability, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: March 9, 1950
  - Item 6: Low-Income Families in the United States, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Edward A. Keller
  - Item 7: National Income and Wealth in the U.S. and in Many Countries Abroad: References, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: U.S. Treasury Department
    Notes: December 1950
  - Item 8: Regional Studies of Income Distribution, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Louisiana State University
  - Item 9: Family Income in Metropolitan Areas, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: February 28, 1964
  - Item 10: Workers Receive 71 Per Cent of National Income Today, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Family Economics Bureau
    Notes: July 26, 1964
  - Item 11: Size of Family Income, By Family Characteristics, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: March 31, 1964
  - Item 12: Low Income Families, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: February 24, 1964
  - Item 13: Distribution of Income, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Gabriel Kolko
  - Item 14: Income and Economic Progress, 1946; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Maxwell S. Stewart
  - Item 15: The Income Revolution, 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Victor Perlo
- Box: 34, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Personal Income, a Key to Small-Area Market Analysis, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Box: 34, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Effects of an Income Tax on Labor Supply, 1968; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Author: Marvin Kosters
  - Item 2: Where the Rich and the Poor People Live, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Author: Homer Hoyt
  - Item 3: Human Capital and the Personal Distribution of Income: An Analytical Approach, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Author: Gary S. Becker
- Box: 34, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Data on Self-Employed Retirement Deduction for Taxable Year 1964, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 18, 1966
- Box: 34, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report to the Congress of the United States, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Box: 34, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Single-Firm Independent Union, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Box: 34, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Single-Firm Independent Union, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Box: 34, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Local Independent Unionism: Two Case Studies, 1961; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Author: Leo Troy
  - Item 2: Management and the Local Independent Union, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Box: 34, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Method of Construction and Calculation of the Index of Retail Prices, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Box: 34, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of the Dearness Allowance Commission on the Question of Adequacy of the Dearness Allowance Admissible to the Central Government Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Author: India Ministry of Finance
    Notes: December 1, 1965
- Box: 34, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: American Indians in California, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: November 1965
- Box: 34, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Roswell Residential Training Center and Related Indian Vocational Education Policy, 1973; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Author: U.S. Congress
  - Item 2: Unemployment Among American Indians, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 10, 1963
  - Item 3: Impact of Grants to Indian Tribes Under the Emergency Employment Act of 1971, 1973; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 14, 1973
- Box: 34, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: El Concepto de Subordinacion, Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
    Author: Edgardo A. Ferrari Costa
- Box: 34, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Alles Uber den Dienstvertrag (Dienstzettel) des Angestellten, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Notes: December 1967
- Box: 34, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Tyosopimuslaki Tyosaantolaki Tyoehtosopimuslaki Laki Tyotuomioistuimesta Laki Tyoriitojen Sovittelusta, 1968; Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Author: Valtion Painatuskeskus
    Language: Finnish.
- Box: 34, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Contract of Service, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Author: Gunther Schelp
- Box: 34, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Contracts of Employment & the IR Act, 1972; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Notes: June 1972
  - Item 2: The Contract of Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Author: R.W. Rideout
- Box: 34, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: To Nullify Yellow Dog Contracts, 1930; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Author: John P. Frey
- Box: 34, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Men Wanted, 1939; Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Author: Paul Garrett
    Notes: June 19, 1939
  - Item 2: Statesmanship in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Profile for Freedom: How Much Freedom Do We Really Have?, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Author: Freedom Studies Project
- Box: 34, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Orienting the New Worker, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Orientation of New Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Author: The Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.
  - Item 3: Initial Employee Orientation, 1968; Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Author: Michigan Department of Civil Service
  - Item 4: Induction, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Author: Roy Van Gelder
- Box: 34, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Shore Excavations Can Be Death Traps, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Author: Workmen's Compensation Board of British Columbia
  - Item 2: Work Accident Rates, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Author: National Safety Council
  - Item 3: Accident Analysis and Remedial Action, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Statistical Analysis of Accidents Reported During the Year 1965, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Author: The Workmen's Compensation Board
  - Item 5: Workmen's Compensation in Hawaii, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Author: Hawaii Department of Labor and Industrial Relations
  - Item 6: Workmen's Compensation in Hawaii, 1969; Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Box: 34, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A 3-Year Look at Eye Injuries in B.C. Industry, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Box: 34, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Injury Rates: New York State Industries, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Box: 34, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Industrial Injury Frequency Rates, 1945; Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: State of Rhode Island Department of Labor - Division of Industrial Inspection, 1948; Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    Author: Rhode Island Department of Labor
  - Item 3: Work Injuries in the United States During 1946, 1947; Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Injury Rates, by Industry, 1966 & 1967, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Report of Work Injuries to Minors Under 18 Years of Age, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Box: 34, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Work Injuryies and Accident Causes in Lunchrooms, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Federal Work Injury Facts, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Discussion of Industrial Accidents and Diseases, 1947; Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: The Operation of Hoisting Apparatus, Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Occupational Hazards to Young Workers, 1942; Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Box: 34, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Industrial Arts in Education, 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    Author: American Vocational Association
- Box: 34, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Directory of New York State Industrial Arts Supervisors and Teachers, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)